http://www.edonation.com/privacy/

Security
The servers that house eDonation.com are maintained in a manner that safeguards the information in our databases effectively.
Personal Information
Unless you voluntarily provide us with any personal information, such as your e-mail address, this site does not collect personal information about you without your knowledge.
When you visit our site, we collect the following information: The name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, yahoo.com, if you are connecting from a Yahoo! account). The date and time you access our site. The Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site or the Internet address of the computer used to link to our site. This information is used for Site Management purposes only.
NOTICE: Unless you choose to provide such information, we do not collect or maintain personal information about you when you visit our site. If you send us an e-mail message or complete a web form containing personal information, we collect and store the personal information which you choose to provide, such as your mailing address, e-mail address and the content of any request for information or any comments you may have.
Use of Information
If you choose to provide any personal information, such as your mailing address or phone number, we may use that information to contact you.
eDONATION CHARGE ON YOUR CREDIT CARD?
eDonation.com, a division of Campaign Solutions, Inc. is a credit card processor for a number of political campaigns, organizations, associations, and non-profit entities.
LOOKUP YOUR CHARGE
©
2020 eDonation.com
All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy
Visit:
CampaignSolutions.com | ConnellDonatelli.com
